screens I did send you.
Did you get a chance to take a look at
them?
Right.
I don't, Jana, as I,
as a friend was telling you,
like I am just starting to see this and
to be able to complete all of those.
Is going to be very messy,
is not going to look right, is not going,
probably is not going to function well
either, but yeah, but go ahead, we are.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I'm not going to go and explain that.
The stories are here.
I've already written the stories, right?
Again,
I'm going to talk to the team tomorrow.
If you can join the grooming,
we can talk in,
if you wanted to understand or review
those, you can please do join, right?
Okay, these are for direct shipments.
So you know the difference between direct
shipments and...
consolidation, right?
These are all for direct shipments.
If it is a direct shipment,
there will be option to the user to see
what is prior and what is new, right?
So the prior and new idea is...
K.
Sorry, sorry to interrupt you.
I have a question,
what is direct shipment?
Direct shipment is shipment with only one
order.
Okay, okay, okay, yes, I remember.
And it has only one route as well, right?
Yeah.
Only one, oh no.
Yeah.
Yeah, one pickup and one drop.
It was one star,
one pickup and one delivery. OK.
Yeah, one pickup and one delivery.
So for that, we have this UI, right?
Where you have, say for example,
the idea is there are,
I'll just quickly explain,
then you will have,
then we can go to consolidation.
That's what I wanted to talk about.
So in a prior, sorry,
in a direct shipment, the view,
if there is an.
order change, this particular shipment,
the user will get a message here.
Right, in this section.
Ugh.
User will get a message in the shipment
exception saying that there is an order
change, right?
They will click on the order change,
and if it is a direct shipment,
it will give them this view.
Right,
what this one is trying to tell them is,
this is your buy shipment,
and these are all the options for the
user. They can cancel an existing tender.
This will appear only when the shipment
has been sent or tendered to a carrier or
accepted by a carrier, right?
A tender to a carrier is sent to a
carrier.
or accepted by a carrier.
This screen is applicable only when the
order changes come,
but the shipment has already been sent to
a particular carrier and the carrier is
evaluating or carrier already accepted
that.
So there are a couple of options for the
user to take.
They can either cancel a tender if it has
already been sent.
they can cancel the tender.
So user takes an action,
it is a canceling A tender, right?
They can keep the tender and re-tender
because there is an update that has come,
right? These are all order updates.
So for example,
if you see here in the shipment,
you have one order. Within that order,
A couple of things can change, right?
Fate can change, volume can change, right?
A pickup address can change,
anything can change.
There are something called transportation
relevant order changes.
If there is a transportation relevant
order changes, right?
So all these are fields related to that.
Transportation order fields, right?
If it's a delivery date, pickup date,
distance, incoterms,
then bill to appointments,
then seed information,
seed equipment information,
any of these information changes, right?
And they can...
and the shipment has been tendered to a
carrier that is sent to a carrier or a
carrier is accepted,
this screen will appear.
So in this particular screen,
they will have actions, cancel, re-tender,
and...
Bypass tender, right? So keep,
you have to read it as keep tender,
read tender. You have to keep the tender.
So it means if it has been sent to CTNS,
you need to retain the CTNS, right?
Bypass means you have sent it to CTNS,
but you don't want to send up.
Update to the carrier,
so you are keeping the tender and you are
bypassing the tender, right?
Bypass tender means you are not updating
or sending information again to the
carrier.
That is what these two actions are, right?
So you will need two buttons here.
In this case, say for example,
in this case, right,
if this is the first carrier,
you don't have CTNS here,
but let's say if this is the last one is
CTNS and this has been sent to the
carrier, tender status is sent, right,
you have a cost for this carrier, 1780,
right? Imagine this is 1780.
Whether you wanted to retain the same
cost for the same carrier, right?
Say the same CTNS is available as a top
carrier in the next,
or in one of the lists right here,
or it might not even be part of the list.
It doesn't matter,
but you're going to plug the CTNS here
and you're going to say.
If the cost is available,
you're going to put the cost here.
If there is no cost,
you're going to leave it blank, right?
And if the user would want to enter a
quote,
user will have an option to enter a quote
here, right?
So what they can do is they can re-tender.
Re-tender means?
If this is CTNS,
current carrier who has sent or accepted
a CTNS,
and the next carrier CTNS is part of the
list, you put the CTNS,
you put the equipment,
what that second new route list has given,
right? You put the route rank, rate,
and tender status.
Right now it doesn't have any tender
status. Here it has sent.
The old list prior is the old list, right?
Which one is prior here? Yeah,
this is prior. The old list is here.
If it is sent here, you keep it as sent.
If it is accepted,
you keep it as accepted.
And in the new list for the same carrier,
you would not have any status because it
is.
A new route list has been generated,
but this carrier is part of the list or
not part of the list, right?
Let's say he's part of the list.
So he's part of the list means you'll
have a rank, you have a route, right?
You have an equipment.
But this carrier is not part of the list.
You will have the same equipment,
but you will not have put the route and
the rank because...
It is not part of the list you are trying
to insert this carrier into the list,
right?
That is why it is always going to give,
it is going to talk about the reference
of the same carrier over in this section.
Right, OK, so if the route.
If the routing was successful,
you would have a pickup date and a
delivery date.
If the routing was not successful,
you will not have a pickup date and a
delivery date. So in that case,
it has to force the user to select a
pickup date and the delivery date.
Right? Okay, so now coming to the cost,
the user can keep the old cost,
can enter a new cost, right?
Or select the new cost and say,
I like this cost, new cost, right?
Or they can completely give a new quote
for this carrier. Right?
So if they select the prior cost,
If it is $1000 and the new one says it is
900,
they can keep the same 1000 for the
carrier, right?
If they have a new cost and it says 1000
and this says 2000,
they can select 2000 and retain this 2000
as it is, right?
They can also enter a quote and select a
quote and enter a.
quote for this carrier and override the
cost.
All these are possible via the screen,
right? We are this option.
And all these are views.
So this is a prior tender view for this
particular carrier.
What is the prior tender view?
What for this carrier,
for the same carrier,
because there was a change,
what did the system return as part of the
new option list?
Right, so the two lists are created.
Right,
so if the user clicks on view tender,
it will take them to the tender page here.
and give them the entire list.
Right here you will have a new list.
In the bottom,
you will have a old prior list, right?
It will give all the details because here
we are just displaying this section,
only this section, right?
So if you see here,
I'm just displaying only this section.
We are not providing entire tender screen.
We're just giving, showing them route,
rank, what is the SCAC, carrier,
equipment, AP cost, tender status,
pickup date, and delivery date.
Only these information are populated for
the prior and the new.
But if they wanted to see all of this,
right, drop carrier, all these.
They need to go to click here,
view tender,
it'll take them to the tender page and
then give them the view of the entire
tender screen for this shipment.
If I go here to the next page,
so it should be collapsible,
so they should be able to collapse the
list and see,
and then you have a compare screen.
Compare screen is all these fields.
What was the old value?
What is the new value? Say, for example,
for this particular ship date.
The ship date or the address got changed.
What was the old value?
What is the new value? It should give,
say that is why you see here prior,
and this is where you see new.
So it should give them the idea of what
has changed for this particular order,
so that the user can verify, oh,
and understand, okay,
these are the things that have changed,
whether they would want to.
cancel the tender, re-tender,
or bypass so they can take a decision
based on that. Does it make sense?
Manuela.
No,
I was saying it's a little bit difficult
to follow because it's a lot of
information.
Yeah, it is a lot of information,
but you know that is why we have also
details in the story.
Maybe you can take a look at it and then
see.
So I've given here buttons or buttons,
action buttons, displays,
these are names for the fields and the
values, right?
And these are corresponding details that
they can select.
For each of these options, right?
And this one says,
if the prior cost is there and the value
is there, this might be displayed,
this might not be displayed.
If the earlier cost was the prior cost
was quoted,
it will show it was a quoted cost as a
information.
This was a rated,
it will not show anything. It will show,
it will be like this.
Right.
How many prior tender lists you have?
There is.
So, you put...
How many prior tender list?
I didn't get your point.
What do you mean prior tender list?
You have a new,
you have a new tender list,
you have a prior tender list.
How many of them are?
How many prior lists are?
Is that list a history of all tenders
that happened? Or what?
Because prior can be many priors,
you know.
Yeah, the recent prior.
You could have only sent one,
say the prior, say,
let's say you have prior two, prior three,
right? In that one, you cannot have sent.
At that point of time,
if you had already moved on to a new list,
it would have been canceled.
I know, I know you cannot because that is,
that's why you have a new,
Yeah.
but I need to understand how many of
those can exist, right?
So you're asking basically a history of
tendering.
It is history of tendering.
You can say history of tendering,
but this prior is recent prior, right?
If you have a tender, there could be like,
say for example, right?
You created a tender list,
then you have a history of the tender.
You could have multiple history, right?
Multiple history of this tender.
but there could be only one sent.
You cannot have sent in the, say,
if you have multiple prior,
imagine this is a prior one and this is
prior two. In the prior one only,
you will have sent. You cannot have sent,
you won't have sent in the prior two
because all those got cancelled.
And that is why you generated a new list.
Right?
You're comparing between a prior and a
Mhm.
new list that has been generated.
That is what you're trying to do here.
Yes, that's what I,
and how many rows have a tender list?
That is another question that I had
before.
It can be any number of rows, right?
I cannot, I don't exactly know,
but it can be like 10 or 15 carriers.
Sometimes it might also return 20
carriers.
At 100.
100, I don't think so. 100.
Those many carriers won't be returned.
Okay, yeah, that is, yeah,
that is why it's a problem to see both
Top 10 or 12.
together, right? If you have too many.
Yeah,
that is why I said right in the view you
need to give like a collapsible thing.
Oh, this one,
you are going to show only the one that
has been accepted or sent. You see here,
you're not going to show everything.
What is the, in the prior,
what is the carrier which has either been
accepted or sent? That is only the one,
because you will always have only one
carrier in the prior which is always
either sent or accepted.
Nothing had happened. In that case,
you just apply the order changes, right?
You accept the order changes, apply it.
If the tender has not been sent or it is
currently under review,
none of the carriers have done anything,
right? It's all cancelled.
You just apply the order changes and
leave it, right?
So it's only when it has been sent or
accepted you will have this question.
Okay, makes sense? Okay.
So this is only when there has been sent
or accepted. Okay,
now we covered all these sections, right?
All these stories kind of, right?
There are a lot of rules within it.
You might, if you read it,
you will understand all the rules. Okay,
we'll go on to the changes itself.
In a multi-stop, right?
We wanted to do a similar thing in,
you can.
bring the same idea in the changes as
well to inform the user what had changed.
But if it is, see,
right now we did talk about only about a
direct shipment, right?
If in case of a consolidation,
you will have multiple orders, right?
As you can see here,
there are multiple orders in this stop.
You have order one.
to then there is another pickup where
you're picking up another order and then
you're dropping all those in the third
stop, right?
In case of a consolidation,
the first view,
this one is to give the user to tell them
saying there is a change, right?
Change to the...
details, changes to the order, right?
I am thinking, I'll leave it to you,
we can discuss,
we can think about the idea, right?
So this order could have changed,
this order could have changed,
or this order could have changed, right?
If it is a multi-stop,
I would probably also want to add these
two fields.
into the stop as well, right?
Planning date type,
what type of planning it is,
whether it is a requested delivery date
planning or scheduled ship date planning.
What is the anchor date?
Anchor date is a logic that we are using
to send it to the routing, right?
So what is the anchor date?
Is it 320 in this case, right?
and then give options to the user because
this plan has changed or the order has
changed,
approve the plan because this will be
applicable even for Optimizer, right?
Optimizer comes or gives a recommendation.
The user needs to review this and approve
the plan, right?
That is why it is called approve the plan
or edit the shipment.
and stops, right?
They should be able to edit shipments and
stops, remove an order,
put a new order in,
whatever they would want to do it,
they should be able to do it. Okay.
Coming to the point right now, right?
So there is an order change.
So since there is an order change,
as I told you, out of these three orders,
any order could have changed, right?
My thought process,
let's take this example where...
This order, 8499, has undergone a change.
The order request had come,
and because of that,
something had changed.
This does not matter if the shipment is
tendered, not tendered, it doesn't matter,
right? So in this case,
we are going to flag it to the user if it
is a multi-stop consolidation.
For the user to make a decision to see if
even if they would want to keep this
order in the shipment, right? So,
in this case,
this particular order has undergone a
change, right? So,
what it will do is it will flag a message
under here saying that P2 say it will say
P2 this pickup.
Atlanta, this is Atlanta, right?
Atlanta update.
So it will show some kind of a message
saying there is an update here for this
pickup stop, right?
If there are multiple orders,
still it will show that in this stop,
it is like it is telling you there is a
change in this particular stop, right?
And then, what are all those changes? So,
it is giving you a summary of those
changes, right? As we did see,
these are all the changes that can happen
on an order, right? A date change,
a location change, a ship date change.
What are all those, right? So,
what it will tell here is it tells the
user there was one location change,
there was a...
Two date change, one weight change,
4 order changes, right? What I'm...
I have a question: Where do you,
where do you edit those?
Where do you do those changes in orders
in the order?
It automatically comes on automatically
comes as an integrated order, right?
Thank you.
The customer between us and customer
there is an integration system they send
post the order update via an integration
UI.
Okay, but who does those changes?
That's what I need to understand and
System, system,
system does those changes in order.
where.
So,
it's a change from an existing order
already, right?
Right.
Okay, based on...
Based on.
That change happened.
Yeah, based on customer, see,
these are all these,
whenever it is in a stock,
it means that we already have an order,
correct? You cannot just have some order,
yeah.
I know, I know, I know, but...
So it means this order belongs to a
customer, right? In this case,
Mhm.
it is Airco, right?
So it belongs to Airco.
Yeah, I know.
So Airco customer has sent an update from
their system.
to order C1.
Okay,
so they initially first sent an order.
After sending an order,
we planned everything.
But after we planned,
they send an update to that order.
They might say like, okay,
initially I planned for this order.
I say I want to send only 10 boxes.
Now it is 15 boxes.
Okay,
so the customer is able to change that
order, right?
Yeah.
Okay, from which platform or what?
Is there any...
from their system.
From their system. OK,
their system sends a message to the
Yeah.
Odyssey system and changes things. OK,
that's something to know. OK.
Correct.
Okay.
Right,
so it is the order domain which will
handle it,
but it'll it'll pass the message to the
shipment domain saying that there is an
order change that had happened.
Makes sense.
Yeah.
Okay, so when that happens,
it is going to capture saying, okay,
there was a location change. If say,
imagine there are multiple orders,
it will give the summary saying there was
four order changes, 4 orders changed.
It could give one way change to date
change. Say, imagine two different orders.
It is going to give all these details,
right, at a high level.
Right,
I am thinking either a tool tip or some
other information.
I leave it to your design,
but this is my idea, right?
At the stop level, it is going to give.
highlights,
highlight of what are all has changed,
right? Then after that, at each...
Each of the order level,
it is going to give the list of the
Joke.
changes, right? So, for that,
in this case, we have only one order,
but in a stop,
there can be multiple orders, right?
If there are multiple orders like this,
can we use the compare screen?
My thought process is we have an option,
give them the compare screen.
And we already know all these are
transportation relevant and they will be
able to see what are all the changes that
had happened between prior and new.
Right?
So the same concept what we saw here,
we can implement here.
So they can click and see for this order.
They can click and see what has changed
for this order, this order, this order.
So in that way,
they can get the whole idea.
right? If there is a weight change, right,
if there is a weight change,
we already have a volume, right?
If the volume changes,
we are going to put an indicator and say
the new volume or something here changed,
right? If this is a gross weight change,
you're going to put an indicator and say
that this new weight has changed.
Right? So those are all, say,
seed equipment. Seed equipment, we don't,
that's okay.
These are the two main things,
weight and volume. If anything changes,
we are going to highlight here,
saying that the weight and volume has
changed.
Right?
Makes sense.
Manuela, you there?
Yeah, I'm listening.
Okay, okay. Yeah,
so these are the changes.
Maybe I will add a warning triangle or
something,
and then I will also add that part.
Say that it also tells you what does the
prior weight change and new weight change
if the weight changed, right?
So in that way,
user can easily identify what are all the
changes. Okay, this is the summary screen.
Those comes,
those changes comes from the same signal,
right? From the same message,
from the customer.
Order, these are all order changes,
correct? All these are order changes here.
Okay, okay.
Consolidation, multi-stop order change.
because it's a multi-stop and there are
multiple orders in each of those stops
and any of those orders can change,
the idea is how can we tell the user
saying what had changed in an order and
how can they review it?
Does it make sense?
Mhm.
It is more like a summary, right?
Looking at the screen,
they should be able to get an idea. Okay.
Next is a more complex part, right?
Now the user wants to take some decision
based on these changes.
Now they understood what is the change,
right?
So they would want to take a decision.
either reviewing it,
they can approve the plan. They say like,
okay, go ahead, that's not a big deal.
Keep the plan as it is,
they can approve the plan.
Or they can edit the shipment, right?
If they go and edit the shipment,
it goes to the next page.
Right.
So here, when they do the edit,
it has three sections in it.
One is the stop section,
which we already did see here.
This is the stop section,
which we already did see.
Maybe we can put a condensed version of
it or show some details around it,
saying like, P1 is Kansas City,
P2 is Atlanta.
Here we have something else.
What is that we have?
Kansas City, P2 is Atlanta,
and P3 is Minneapolis, right?
So we have P3 as Minneapolis.
So these three are details,
and what are the orders mapped around it?
So this is an order stop information.
The next section is stop details, right?
Each of these flow, it is...
Say, in this case.
In this case, we have P2 as change, right?
Say, for example, user selects P1.
If they select P1, by default,
it will be selected to P1. So,
if it selects to P1, what it will tell us,
these are all the order which are,
you know, mapped to this particular.
P1 stop, right? So,
these are stop details.
Stop details means order assigned, sorry,
not stop details,
order assigned to this particular stop,
right? For this pickup stop,
I have these two orders,
so it's going to give you orders.
The third one is search. Say, for example,
the user feels that there is an
opportunity to...
add one more order to the stop, right?
Either to this pickup stop or this pickup
stop. They can search any of the order.
So there is 3 sections available.
I'll tell you what is the use of it,
then you will get the overall picture.
Does it make sense? This is a stop.
These are orders specific to the stop.
So if I click P1.
these two will get loaded.
If the user clicks P2,
this particular order will get loaded
here.
So they will have an option to move or
remove, right? Move is more an action,
drop and move it.
I'll tell you why and how this will
function, right? And the third one is.
Searching an order.
Right? While searching,
it needs to go and look for all the
shipments. Shipments in all the shipments,
both in monitoring as well as in shipment
exceptions.
All the shipments it needs to pull.
Right here, so that is the idea, OK?
Any questions here?
Okay.
Trying to understand yet.
Yeah, once I complete,
then you will get some idea about it,
right? Okay, so now regarding the stops,
so I've given the logic here, right?
So regarding the stops,
you can see that the stops will have,
here we don't see, but here, right?
So here you can see that.
There are buttons handles where the user
can move. Say, for example,
the user would want to move P2 to P1 and
P1 to P2, right? They can drag and do it,
so they wanted to retain the same order,
but the order needs to be picked up first
instead of P1 being these two orders
being picked up.
up so they can drag and move it here
automatically. P1 gets adjusted here.
So this becomes P1 and P1 becomes P2.
Make sense?
I've written here.
User should be able to drag and drop the
stops, right? Moving stops.
It is just like in the columns what we
had, right? This one, this option.
Like here,
I should be able to drag and move it so
it organizes the same idea.
The by shipment gets moved to some other
spot, right? The same idea.
I should be able to move P2 to P1 and P1
to P2.
Make sense so far?
I am pretty lost in that part, actually.
Okay.
Okay, this part is stop adjustment.
You are keeping the order as it is,
but you are just moving,
you are making P2 as P1 and P1 as P2.
Right, I can also make P2 as P3.
So in that case, I'm moving P2 to...
Last pickup, right? Ideally,
it will not happen.
You should have a delivery towards the
end,
but there I'm just moving and you know
trying to readjust it, right?
The logic will come.
You cannot have a pickup in the last
without the delivery.
Some logic will come, right?
I will write all the logic.
But the idea is the user should be able
to readjust it. Make sense?
But which user is able to do that? That's.
..
Yeah, that is why we had this button,
right? You remember?
We talked about this button.
Edit shipment stops, right?
Once the user clicks on this edit
shipment stop,
because they have reviewing the stages,
they are not approved,
they are not okay with this plan,
which the order changes came in.
So then they are landing up on this
screen, right,
where they have stop information,
then the details of each of the stops.
and orders that they can add to the stops.
Make sense? No?
Which user is whoever is reviewing it?
And why a user needs to change the stops?
Because the order change had come,
they are not happy with the change and
they feel that this plan cannot be ex.
Sorry, I didn't my question. Sorry,
my question was not OK. My question is.
Correct.
What's why? What's the I mean?
That means you're going to have a second
stop empty.
No, it is not second stop empty.
You are moving P1 to P2, right?
So when you move it,
say I am dragging and moving it.
It is not going to be P1.
This is going to be P1, right?
This is going to be moved up.
Right? Imagine you are doing the same way,
right?
You are moving it here and trying to go
put it in between. What happens?
This comes in between, right?
What happens here?
Something else fails to stop.
That means, yeah,
that means the other ones are going to
fail,
but that means the other ones are going
to be assigned to the different stuff,
right? That's okay.
Exactly, exactly. So this is going to be,
if I drag this and put it underneath P2,
so this becomes P1 and this becomes P2.
Makes sense.
Uh huh.
Okay.
Right,
so that is what the user is trying to do,
right?
They also have an option to add a pickup
stop or add a delivery stop.
Right, say they already have two pickups.
They wanted to add one more pickup.
They click on this and the P3 is added
after P2.
Right?
If they wanted to add one more delivery,
they can add delivery, click on delivery,
and after D1, they can add D2.
That is also possible. One is rearranging,
the other one is addition. Make sense?
Okay.
Right,
so those are the options what the user
can do. Okay, say, in this case,
for example,
if the user does not want to execute,
remove this order, right? Say,
for example, they can select on P1.
Once the P1 on the P1,
you have two orders.
Right?
So this will show up on the middle
section here.
So it will show this order 1097,
108497 and 108498.
These 2 orders are here.
Then you have two options for this.
It will show the weight of this
particular stop and the volume of this
particular stop.
Right?
What it will do is user will have an
option to remove the order.
So it means that it gets removed from the
stop itself, from the shipment itself.
So they can either remove an order or
they can move an order.
So if I click on P1,
so it going to populate,
I'll cover the movement first.
So from P1, I wanted to, I can drag,
sorry, sorry,
I can take the shipment and move it to
another stop, P2, right?
So I will drag here and then move it to
P2.
Imagine I wanted to move order 108497
from P1 to P2, right? In this case,
I can select on this particular thing and
then drag and move it.
So that is why I have the option to move
from here to here. Make sense?
Are you getting it?
You get it?
Game, I mean, so many micro interactions.
Yeah, see,
this is this is for the user to this this
Um, yeah.
section is to move the stops or add a
stop. Here is remove an order, right?
Remove an order or move an order.
That is for this section, middle section.
I don't want to put everything in one
thing.
right,
then it'll be too much to handle in one
small thing.
So that is why I separated these two,
right?
They can select any of these and then
they can either remove or move or do
whatever it is. Move is here,
remove is here.
This is specific to orders,
these are specific to stops.
Okay.
Jana, I have a concern.
I need to tell you this,
and I'm going to say that to Laurie as
well.
Mhm.
There is a lot of micro interactions,
and everything is doable,
and I know everything is important, right?
But for an MVP with one week, two weeks,
Mm.
scope, I'm sorry, is...
I don't think it's going to be possible
to do it for that time.
Yeah, you need.
Or if I do it, or if I do it, you know,
is not going to work.
It is going to be a mess, right?
So what I suggest to you,
and I'm going to suggest to Laurie as
well, is...
do a user research,
the same idea that they proposed, right?
And ask users what's the absolute
necessary things that you need for an MVP,
right?
What's the most important parts that you
This is the same.
are using, right? Because...
I am a little bit surprised that you,
you guys being in in Odyssey One like two
years ago, and you also, you, you,
and still, you know,
user management is still in progress,
orders was still in progress.
And right now, within one month,
he wants to do like...
60 or 8, 70% of the work missing, right?
That's what's surprising to me.
Yeah.
That is not okay. I mean,
and that is not my fault. I'm sorry,
and I cannot do anything about it.
As I said,
if I do something and if it goes wrong,
I'm sorry,
it's I cannot do something about it
because it humans humanly is not possible,
right? It's...
See,
that is why I'm asking you to give a
design.
We don't even have to put it on Vercel,
The.
right?
I can explain in the story and give it to
No, no, no, that is not a problem.
That is not a problem. I mean,
the team.
putting it in Versal is actually easier
than doing a design, right?
You can explain it to the team,
but if it's going to work or not,
we don't know. Because if I do it,
if I do this,
and I just do it like whatever,
because I don't,
most of the things is going to take me a
while to understand.
then you have the risk that is going to
be a mess, right? That is,
that afterwards we're going to have, oh,
but this is not working properly. Oh,
this is not looking fine. Oh, I mean,
this doesn't make sense in a lot of buts,
Say it is not going to be 100%, right?
So it is going to evolve. See,
right? And we...
this is my idea.
If you find a better idea to make
adjustments to the stops and orders, yeah,
welcome, right? This is my idea,
my design, right?
It's fine. It's not about the design.
It's what I'm trying to say is about
understanding the problem.
Because to decide something,
I need to understand first, right?
And I don't think...
Correct.
Like, if I sit to understand everything,
I need to do a lot of, you know,
testing as well to understand if some
ideas work or not, right?
Correct.
And that process is pretty long to do.
It's not easy.
Correct. This is not easy.
That is what I am saying.
And then you have to validate it. Yeah,
but...
Order changes handling is not easy.
I am, I am, I'm telling you,
I know it's not easy,
that is not a problem.
The problem is that timing is not
feasible. That's what I'm saying, right?
And I need to understand why you're
trying to do this one month,
one month on the end of the line,
while you have all the two years to.
to figure all this out, right?
And I cannot be responsible for that
because I'm just saying it's not going to
be as expected, right? That is the thing.
Yeah, see.
I need to be responsible for you.
Team is ready to do it. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
See, team is ready to do it.
I also told them that this piece is going
to be complex.
They're asking for a solution.
I told Laurie, Laurie also knows about it,
all this complexity.
They're still keeping the date as October.
So, see,
we are giving it a try and trying to see
that.
all these going to come together and the
team is able to complete it, right?
So if you feel complex and if you feel
that you need more time,
you need to voice it to Laurie, right?
So I am confident that I will be able to
give a solution,
but if the design or team is not able to
do, then we need to figure out what else.
will need to happen, right?
So I will leave it to you to think about
it and if you feel like it is complex,
it is going to take a time to do it and
all those things,
why is your concern to Laurie?
Yeah, of course I'm going to rise. I mean,
I don't,
it's pretty obvious from here that.
It is going to take longer,
much longer there than I was talking
about.
And my,
the thing that I'm going to try to do,
as I told you, is not going to look good.
It's not going to look functional either,
right? It's going to be enough to say,
okay, it's done,
but I'm just warning you and I'm going to
tell this to Laurie as well.
That probably is not going to work.
Right,
this part is not going to be as useful as
we did other things so far. For example,
shipments is, it's not perfect,
but it's for on my perspective,
shipment so far is pretty well made,
right? From this point towards the end,
toward these other things,
I don't think it's going to be the same
quality or the same quality.
you know, usability, right?
I am just raising the flag now, right?
Correct, correct. See,
I've already told Laurie, right?
For that. Yeah.
I have told her all this complexity
involved, right? So she's aware of it.
I already told her,
that's why I told you yesterday also,
right? If you put one time,
tell Laurie that you would want time,
you want time to do it.
So that is why I told you yesterday also
as if.
I know that it is complex, it's not easy,
right? And see,
you have to understand and give a design.
Team has to understand and develop. So I..
.
Right,
there are some things that are involved
in all these pieces.
It is not like I give a design,
it's going to come out.
Okay. Yes,
because whatever we deliver to the
development team,
then they are going to have to, you know,
they're going to have issues as well
because of this, right? And as you said,
They have to understand as well.
yeah, and for example,
right now in orders,
Or Ramesh is still asking me for those
details, like, where is the, you know,
the label change, whatever. For this one,
is not,
I already told Ramesh to stop doing that
because I don't have time. Yeah,
that is part of front end work,
not my work. So, and for this part,
is not going to be like that.
That's the other thing, right?
For this part is I am going to do
Sadick.
something like a sketch that is probably
is going to fail and...
If there are micro, you know, fixes,
that is not going to fix it, right?
Because problems are going,
it's like technical debt.
There is going to be a lot of technical
debt from UX perspective and from
development perspective as well.
I'm pretty sure about that.
Yeah, T.
Yeah, yeah, 100%. No doubt about it,
right? So again,
I'm saying Laurie knows about it,
Nirab knows about it.
So what they want is they don't want a
nice looking piece in the first state,
right?
They wanted to improve it as we go along,
but they want something they would be
able to push it out and then improve on
it.
That's the problem.
It's not going to be an improvement.
It's going to be a restructure later,
right? For this part at least.
We are going to push it and...
And then instead of improving it,
we're going to need a restructure, right?
A rethink of everything,
like redone of everything, right?
We did something similar with shipments.
We did it with you pretty fast.
Do you remember the first part of
shipments? We had a month or so,
Yeah, yeah.
and we did a lot of things.
And then I said, okay,
we need to review it.
We need to fix some stuff that doesn't
make sense, right?
Yeah.
And I need to make sense.
It's not about looking good,
it's about making sense, right?
That is the problem.
And I did the fix and then everyone
complained, like...
Oh, so why you did the fix and everything,
right?
So that is the type of work that is going
to be needed afterwards, right?
A restructure is not going to be able to,
you know,
and that is why I'm calling it technical
debt. Technical debt is about that.
It's not about improving.
It's more about restructuring, right?
So...
What you can do with this,
if what you can do with this part is, yes,
you're going to be able to gain some,
how do you say, political power,
because you're going to say, oh,
we made it. That is fine.
That is also valid.
That is not a bad thing, right? But.
You have to just make sure everyone is
aware that, oh,
so probably this is going to be,
this is going to be needing and
restructuring afterwards, right?
That's all I am saying right now.
Yeah.
Agree, you agree, yeah?
Okay.
We don't know,
it might work out well as well. Who knows,
right?
We are trying to do our best, right?
So I've thought about all this design,
how it would work and how user-friendly
it could be.
All right, so it might work,
it might require some changes based on
user feedback.
So that is going to happen on any product,
right? The best product you give,
still the user might find it in a
different way, saying that, okay,
let's do it in a different way, right?
So that is going to happen. We never know.
Unless we try something and give them out.
give the product out, we don't never know,
we can never get a user feedback.
Yeah, that that is not a problem,
but whenever I'm telling you from my
perspective, my technical perspective,
is whenever you do something like that
and there is a change based on user in in
well well matured products is not very
hard because you already have things that
are defined that you can reuse and.
just do some tweakings right for that.
That is not a problem. But in this,
in the case of this one,
it's going to be different because the
user is going to, for example,
request something or something is not
going to work.
It's not going to be like a tweak.
It really is going to be like a new
sprint of fixing a lot of things from the
ground.
That is what is going to happen, right?
Yeah,
that is why we are going to take
Odyssey's advice as well.
So it is not like we are working
something in dark and we're just
releasing it, right?
So we are going to show it to the user,
get their feedback. No,
at least not user means user,
but at least to Dave,
because Dave has been,
he is the one who built all the system.
right, in the legacy.
So the concept of this is very not
exactly same.
Drag and drop functionality is not there,
but the idea is there.
They should be able to move a stop.
They should be remove an order,
put a new order in.
All these are concepts which are there in
legacy.
So he knows that all these are there.
I'm not bringing any new ideas or
thoughts into it, right?
The way or approach how to do it might be
different than TMS.
I am trying to build it as intuitive as
possible for the user to do it.
That's all I'm trying to do here, right?
But the idea and concepts are very
similar to that of the TMS.
They are able to do it right now.
So we cannot release a product without
those functions.
So that is what I'm trying to tell you.
I understand that.
I totally understand that because we are
rebuilding TMS basically, right?
Yeah.
Okay, what do we do? Proceed.
I'll try to complete it, right?
And then you can think about it,
review it,
and then tell me how we go about it.
But this screen is important.
First is these screens are important for
direct shipments,
and these are screens for consolidation.
Give me one moment, Jana.
I'm gonna call you back.
I need to talk with someone. I'll be back.
OK.
Okay.
Hello!
Hey, Manuela.
Janardhana.
Sorry about that.
I needed to speak with someone.
No problem, yeah.
Okay, we can continue.
Okay.
Okay, we'll go to the section.
So the first section,
this one we did talk about,
it is moving the stops itself.
The other one is the user will select
each of these stops and then either
remove an order, remove an order,
or move an order, right?
So in case of move an order,
they will select
The P1, in this case,
P1 will populate with these two orders,
and they can drag and move it to P2,
or if they add another pickup stop,
they can move this to another pickup stop,
right?
They can do all those changes using this
functionality, right? Okay,
Mmh.
what if the user...
added a stop, right,
a pickup stop or a delivery stop,
then they would want to add an order.
So this third section of the screen is
going to help them to add it.
If you see here on this third section,
right?
Okay, I did. Okay, where is that?
On.
Okay, I gave you an example.
Let me jump here.
So add an order to the shipment.
So what you can do is...
Search customer, origin, destination,
order by shipment,
and shipment status and tender status.
These are all the columns that will be
visible from here from.
this table, right?
This is exactly the same table that we
are going to bring here,
but we are going to show only these
information, right? Customer, origin,
destination, order number, by shipment,
shipment status, and tender status.
These are the columns that we are going
to show. For this column,
the user will be able to search
for any shipment which is not in tender,
right? It is not tendered yet.
Or if it is intended,
you cannot add that shipment into the
list.
It will prevent the user from adding it
into the list because if it is tendered,
you cannot move a shipment from,
you cannot move an order from another
shipment to here because it's already
been tendered.
Right, so send or tender,
so you cannot do that.
So it is for user to identify which are
the shipments which are not tendered or
which is not sent or accepted.
In any other state,
they should be able to move that
particular order from that shipment to
here.
Right, in that case, it will add.
So this screen will help them to add it
into the section here, right?
So it will show up like saying this was
added,
this particular order got added here,
right? This order and this order.
Okay.
Now coming to what the user can do is,
once this order is available,
added to this,
they can move this order into any of
these, right? The order is available,
they can drag and drop it into any of
these stops.
It can move into any of these stops.
The user can drag and drop it here,
or drag and drop it here,
or drag and drop it here.
So they can move it into any of these
stops.
So that is where I've written all this
logic here.
I've given the comments saying how this
will happen, right?
Okay, where do I go then? Remove,
I already explained it to you,
how it will get removed. Remove this,
it will get removed and move into the
third bucket, third column.
If the user clicks on this particular,
this one,
if this is there in the pickup and the
delivery,
it will get removed from the shipment and
then it will go
Into the list here,
so that the user can add it and bring it,
say, for example,
by mistakenly they removed it,
they should be able to add and bring it
inside,
so that is why it gets removed and kept
outside here, right? So,
in this list now going on here.
This we covered, add new stops,
add order to the shipment,
add order to the shipment. Yeah,
we did cover this part,
add order to the shipment.
And before they can finalize, right,
the user had made a lot of changes, right?
So it is going to tell the user saying
what are all the changes they have made.
Right? Order 108499 moved from P2 to P1,
P2 to P1, added stop P3,
order changed 1088501 added to the
shipment.
So all these are recorded as part of the
changes that had happened so that the
user can see
before they can finalize it.
So it will tell shipment impact,
the weight of the shipment has changed,
the volume of the shipment has changed,
who is the current carrier, right?
If they have a current carrier,
it is going to tell them who is the
current carrier, all those, right?
And then the user would go and finalize
this.
Here.
Not this one, edit we go, edit stop.
So here this will change into finalize
approved plan.
So they will go and click on the approved
plan and it will get approved.
Okay,
what are some of the validation errors
that can happen? Right,
these are some of the messages that can
happen.
Delivery stop cannot occur before the
pickup stop.
Because say if you cannot have a delivery
stop before a pickup, right?
So I told you about an example.
So immediately it lasts to tell the user
Okay.
saying that this validation message,
you try to create a delivery stop before
a pickup stop that cannot happen.
Try to look into it, right? Similarly,
order 108501.
pickup date exceeds the requested pickup
window, right?
So that will be another message.
So if the requested date on the order is
particular date and they have asked to
pick up on a different date,
it is going to throw a message, right?
Yeah, sorry. Sort of on Manuela.
Okay,
shipment weight exceeded the equipment.
capacity by 2000 pounds.
So all this will be different validation
messages which will tell the user what
are all the messages that is going to
appear.
Right? Okay.
Then once the user finalizes it,
so this is where the user will go and
finalize this particular thing,
approve the plan,
and they will approve it.
Does it make sense? This is my idea.
So if you have any other thought process,
a better way to do it, you know.
You're welcome. We can discuss about it.
Yeah, I need to, I need to look at it.
I have so many questions, like...
Go ahead, I mean, anyways,
I'm not going to be able to understand
everything now.
Yeah, so I've given all the comments here,
right? Different comments.
That's why I try to add different sheets
and give comments related to it,
why and what it is required.
Take a look at it.
I will send these details to you, right?
All these details.
I have not written stories,
but I'll give you, send you.
Um...
can come up with these questions.
Okay, before wrapping up, I like to,
I like from you to give me a description,
a general description of everything that
we saw today. It's only one thing, right,
that we are seeing,
which is order editing, right? From.
It is not order editing, order changes,
reviewing the order change.
Order changes, yeah, of course, yeah,
but they.
Order changes,
reviewing an order changes for direct
shipment and reviewing the order changes
for multi-stop,
multi-stop or any this one,
multi-stop order changes or aggregation.
Okay,
so those are changes come from the same
source, right?
We are talking about the same.
It's just that from how it affects each
different sales.
Shipment.
Yeah,
how would that affects the shipment
Yeah, it.
because some order has changed and how
would it affects the shipment?
Okay,
so let me put it in words and tell me if
I'm wrong or if I'm missing something.
I'm going to give you a general
description of what I understood, right?
You are describing here in this meeting
Sure.
order changes, right, for
stops, how order changes affect the stops,
right,
and the actions that it can be taken,
and how order changes affect the
tendering.
Yeah, in general, to put it very simple,
right,
Mhm.
how an order change impacts a shipment
which is tender sent or tender accepted,
and how the user should review it.
How the user should, yeah, OK,
and for stops is the same, right?
Is it stops as part of the shipping
information?
Stop is part of the shipment, correct?
Okay.
It is giving them a holistic picture
saying, hey,
these orders are in different stops.
These are all the changes, right?
Imagine you have to go and look into the
order,
and then you have to pick up old order,
and then you have to see what are the
changes.
So we are trying to bring all those
screens in to fit into this so that the
user can.
quickly verify, view,
and see all these changes that have
happened and take a decision right in the
screen. That's all we are trying to do.
Okay.
That's fine.
Um, okay, that's it.
One more thing, Janardhana, from you.
We should close this one now.
What else is the things that I owe you?
I got lost a little bit in the things
Yeah.
that I owe you, right? This is 1.
This is the other one.
This one.
This one we have done, this one. Yeah,
this one you, this one you have to do,
and this one, this particular.
But we, okay, but that is today. I mean,
before this, all of this meeting.
Could you do a summary of the things that
I still owe you?
Um...
Yeah, yeah, I'll do that.
Code you have completed, right?
Code you need to add the code to this
Ohh.
particular thing instead of the...
Yeah, go,
could you could you click on one of the
rows and click on the on the shipment
number, not the left?
This one?
No, no, no, there you go. Yeah,
as you can see, you can edit it now.
There is a button to edit. You click edit.
So yeah, it's opening the quote, right?
Go back. You can go back. Oh, no, sorry.
Yeah, that's fine.
This needs to be changed a little bit.
Yesterday we did talk about it, right?
So cost, we don't want all the cost.
We wanted to display this particular cost
information from the top, right?
And then give the user this particular
view so they can open and see it, right?
We did talk about this one yesterday,
remember?
You don't want like this;
it is better to display the same thing as
the user is seeing here,
and then they should be able to see this
entire block.
But I thought that part was for editing,
actually, for editing.
You wanted to edit or you just want to
see more details.
Yeah,
edit is you're going to open the edit
page, right?
That is what you're trying to do.
But I'm saying this portion,
they should be able to see it as it is
here.
Right, if you see my design, I look here.
Yeah, Seerla.
I did say hyperlink on the or not this
one stops cost. Yeah, cost.
You need to show this one and then you
need to show this values.
We are showing those fields, I believe.
I make sure we are showing those fields.
It's not looking the same thing because
that is a different view, right?
Yeah.
That is why it says inform details.
It's not the same view,
but if you see the cost,
the fields are the same.
Fields are the same;
this section is missing.
Right, this section is missing.
Okay, okay,
so you need the details as well, right?
Yeah.
Not only. So my question is again here,
Janardhana,
why do you need to be redundant in both
places?
Right, from,
because from what I understood,
See, you're opening it as...
that this part,
this part is is to show it in overall
details, right?
That that is the its function,
and why I am telling you this,
because what I want to avoid is to have
redundancy every time, right?
If I do the same thing here.
then we are having two exact same views
for, you know,
it doesn't make sense to have repeated
views. That's what I am trying to say.
Why I need it is here they are not going
to edit it, right?
Only here they will edit it. In that case,
they would need to see the breakdown of
this particular cost.
You don't, you don't.
And why not put the edit both button here
inside of, inside of post, not, not there,
see, but...
Okay, we did talk about this yesterday.
What happens is if you put the edit
button, then it shifts the page to here,
right? And then if they have to open,
they have to click and open here.
They are losing the continuity.
If you can fix that, that's fine.
No, no, no, you go open the edit,
open the edit.
Could you open the edit again?
Okay.
Instead of closing it,
go to the back button.
There is a back button on the top.
There you go.
Click on it. There you go,
you see it again.
Mm.
Right, so you can edit it,
you can edit it, you can save it,
Here, see.
and then go back to this view.
Correct. Here,
they don't see the breakdown, right?
They see only the summary, right?
They can see accessorials is 394, right?
Then they have to click here to view the
breakdown of it, right?
If there are other things.
And why we don't, okay,
why we don't put just put a button that
says view more and that takes you to the
to the to the top right to the cost top.
Yeah, that is also possible.
If you wanted to do it that way,
it should have,
that's the exact reason why I kept it as
saying hidden, right?
Okay, okay,
I will do that because I don't like
Like this, like this option.
because I I you have to understand I
don't it's not a good idea to to repeat
the views over and over again, right?
If if we show everything here and we show
everything in the tab then.
Both are repeated, right?
I should do a copy-paste instead.
Yeah, both are repeated,
but the context is different, right? See,
That is the thing.
what I'm saying is a lot of the
information is repeated. Say,
if you see here,
this information cost is available
somewhere else, right?
We are showing the cost,
but a holistic perspective is not
available. See,
you are looking at this one with the
shipment details,
so your thought process might change why
this cost for this particular.
thing because when it is in, you know,
different mode or different things and
all these things are changing, right?
So you're viewing it as a complete thing.
When you're viewing it as a complete
thing, sometimes your idea might change.
All right,
so the perspective will change based on
how we are viewing it.
That is the, I agree with it,
I agree with it,
but then for for that's why I am saying
instead of showing everything there,
we can just put a button and that routes
you to the, you know,
details that we already have here, right?
Yeah, that is also fine.
If you can make it happen,
Okay.
saying that it pops up or do something,
you know,
that is where in my design also I didn't
display all of it, right?
I just put this one.
But if the user would want to see the
details,
they should have an option to see it.
Right,
I'm not asking you to display it all the
time. This is summary.
If they would want to see it,
Okay.
similarly stops, right?
So you would put some,
you're not going to display the stops
altogether.
You're just going to say something saying
that it is getting picked up from this
location to this location, right?
If the user would want to see all of this.
Ohh.
Right,
they click on it and then it takes pants.
Right, so that is the idea.
We don't want to give all of it and one
it's as compressed as possible,
but if they want to see more detail,
it should there should be an option for
it.
Okay.
Okay, so this one,
I think you are kind of done,
but you know, small tweaks here and there.
So this one and then the other one is...
order changes, right? This part,
this part needs to be worked on and what
Yeah, but that is today, right?
We we talked about today, so that is...
else I have. Let me go.
No, this one is from the earlier one,
right? Direct.
Ohh, okay, okay, okay, okay,
so that is different.
Yeah,
this order change is direct shipment
order change,
and this one is consolidated order change.
But, but we talked about this yesterday,
right? Direct shipment order.
I explained it to you. Yeah,
I explained it to you today how it works,
but you know,
I sent all the design or stories because
stories were returned and all those
things were given to you before.
That's what I was asking you before.
Both are separate, right? Direct,
direct or change and consolidated are
Yeah.
different, right? Just separate. Okay,
we have two there. What else?
Different, yeah, concept is different.
Right there, yeah, one second.
Let me see my story.
This one is done a drop carrier.
We have drop carrier.
Drop carrier? No, I don't think so.
What is the what is the top drop carrier?
Drop carrier,
we did talk about it right within the
tender.
we need to provide the drop carriers,
which are the carriers dropped,
which did not come up, make up this list.
Right,
so there are drop carriers in the bottom.
Oh, okay.
with a view, collapsible view,
then it can expand and show.
It's like this.
Yeah, okay, I remember that one.
So drop carriers are is about the
Yeah.
carriers that didn't, didn't able,
weren't, yeah,
Make up to the list.
they weren't able to get to the pickup
list, right?
Correct, exactly.
They are dropped for some other reason,
right? OK, so that is done,
Uh-huh.
so tender page. OK, one second,
just what is this tender page,
delete code, this one right on.
this particular screen,
instead of add quote here,
I would need add quote here.
Right?
Because the user is going to select on an
option and add a code.
They are going to override this rate
using this option. So it is like if the,
you know,
here you have another option if you can
see here. Where is that code page?
Man, it's so scarier.
Scoped or not others.
I did that one go.
Carrier quoted, you have this option,
right? So when you say yes,
it means someone has went here as
overridden this particular rate with a
quoted rate, right?
Quoted rate is the exact way in which
they would edit.
or add a quote, right? This is what it is.
So when a user goes and adds a quote,
so instead of button being here,
this option should be here.
Right, add a quote.
Okay, so yeah,
I had a question about that and I just
remembered.
So add a quote was about collecting
multiple, you know, carriers and...
adding a quote for them, right?
So to send them a quote.
Not multiple carriers,
that is not multiple carriers.
You are going and adding a code for each
option.
You cannot do multiple carriers in one go.
So it's not like a bidding, like say, oh,
I am sending you a proposal,
That is, yeah, that is that is spot.
would you like? But yeah,
but that proposal is, okay, that is fine.
Yeah, that is part.
Okay, let's, I'm gonna do the change test.
is gonna be for each one. What else? That,
okay.
Each one. Yeah, within this, right,
if they have not added a quote,
they didn't start,
they are using just a rate.
This would be no, right? The rate here,
we have yes and no, yes and no.
This logic, if you want,
you can adjust it, that's fine. Otherwise,
I have written in the story, right?
So this will be no if they not even added
a quote.
And if they are going to add a quote,
it will show add quote instead of editor
quote. Right here,
because you see you have a yes,
Uh.
it is showing as an editor quote.
The logic is correct, right?
But if they have not even added a quote,
it should say add a quote.
If they have added a quote earlier,
they wanted to edit it,
it will say edit quote.
quote and there should be an option to
delete the quote, right?
Delete a quote is it will remove the rate.
Make sense?
Three options so that those are the
things that will happen as part of the
quote.
Okay.
Okay,
so that needs to be updated or tells.
I think these are the ones, right?
By shipment you already completed.
That's okay, right? This we already have.
Yeah, these are the ones right now.
Okay, so we have four in total.
Yeah, four in total, right? Add edit code.
You have pretty much have more have most
Right, OK.
of it. This needs to be small changes.
Drop carrier needs to be added, right?
I've, yeah, drop carrier.
You might have to add one small thing in
the design.
I will write the story or recommendation
for it, how it needs to be done, right?
It is this particular thing, right?
If you see here,
it's called the process CAC option.
Right? So if there is, yeah,
this particular thing,
Okay, but...
you need to add these two boxes into
where a user should be able to add into
this particular list any carrier and SCAC,
right?
The carrier will be provided by this
particular list.
It'll be calling the master data and
getting all the list of carriers.
So I can pick any carrier and I can
choose any of the equipment,
what they have, right? If you see here,
this carrier is only TL,
so I can go and add it, right?
So it comes into the list.
So that option I would need it.
I will put a story for that one.
Right, see, this carrier got added, right?
So you need to provide me an way in the
screen, right? Either here,
replace this with the add carrier.
Add carrier,
once the user selects on add carrier,
this box will enable and they should
select a SCAC or equipment.
Right, and add it.
But that is a different thing, right? You,
you didn't...
Yeah, new, there's a new requirement.
You didn't?
Okay, let's not talk about it right now.
Let's put it that for later.
It.
Okay.
So can we just list the four?
It's coding individually,
that's the first one. For the tendering,
right?
Yeah, drop carrier.
Drop carrier.
Drop carrier, then you have this.
order change, right?
Order changed for direct shipment.
All right.
This one, direct shipment order change.
And order change for consolidated, right?
Consolidated. I don't have the stories,
but I have the design.
Alright, so I'll give you the design.
Maybe once you complete all this,
you can start working on the design.
I mean, in the meantime,
I can add stories,
but I'm not sure how your design is going
to come.
Are you going to follow this design or
are you going to follow it?
You're going to create a new design for
it.
No, I don't think.
Some things I can follow it,
maybe adding the buttons, for example,
right? But for the other complex ones,
I don't know.
I don't even know how it's going to turn
out.
That is why I don't know how to write the
stories, right?
How your design is going to come out.
Is it going to be the same design or is
it going to be a different design?
Otherwise, right?
I will write something and your design
will be doing something else. See,
if you're going to follow this pattern,
I'm going to write the same thing, right?
I've given all the comments,
how it's supposed to function,
all those here.
I try to explain as much as possible in
this one.
But if your design is not going to come
out the same way as what I am writing,
then I have a lot of rework to on the
stories, right?
Yeah,
but I cannot guarantee anything because I
Yeah.
told you it's a process that needs to be
groomed, that needs to be,
and we are skipping all that basically.
So I'm just telling you it's going to
show something and that's it.
Probably I won't be able to understand it
Yeah.
myself.
In the end, so OK,
so which one of those four are is your is
your is the priority is your priority
right? I need to understand.
Yeah, first is code, right?
You've this one you can do it.
Give me one second.
Give me one second. I lost the chat.
Where is the chat?
Yeah,
I will I will add the priority here in
the chat.
Okay, quotes, here's the list.
Ought.
That's just code,
then next is drop carrier.
And 3rd is order change direct.
Shipment and forth this order change
consolidation.
Yeah, these are the ones.
Okay.
Right,
and then you have small changes that you
need to do, small changes on.
shipment, right?
Cross-section and...
Right.
Like, what?
Post and stops.
Top section.
Section.
Showing details, details, right?
button addition.
You said you're going to add a button,
right?
Okay, I'll just leave it like that.
I don't know how it is going to come out,
but...
written. So these are the ones.
Okay.
Pitch.
Edit.
That is on shipment detail.
Yeah, you want to say shipment page,
shipment details page. OK.
Okay.
OK, John.
Yeah,
this is how the priority is going to be,
Uh, that's him.
yeah.
Okay, I'll let you know how it goes.
Sure, yeah.
And.
Okay, I'll send you the design as well,
right?
I think I've sent you the rest of the
ones,
but I'll just send this one consolidation,
right?
And send me the stories as well,
the numbers, but so I can find them,
Jeremy.
Yeah, stories for direct directors here.
For everything that we have there.
Okay, for quote, I'll put it here, quote.
What is this?
Catman.
From carriers.
This.
Auto change.
Is this?
But pizza.
Real magic smoking it out.
Details page view.
This, this one.
Okay, I've added those.
Right, okay.
If they think it's going.
Okay.
How is your overflow board coming?
Are you done with the overflow board?
Thank you.